{"sid": "FZRIEU91QM54_main", "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 6, "start_time": 423841, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 423842, "question": "3+6+47", "correct_answer": 56, "events": [["submit", 428947]], "time_left_end": "295", "answered_time": 428947, "user_answer": "56", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "295", "question_time_start": 428948, "question": "4+3+37", "correct_answer": 44, "events": [["submit", 434751]], "time_left_end": "290", "answered_time": 434751, "user_answer": "44", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "290", "question_time_start": 434752, "question": "9+3+7+3", "correct_answer": 22, "events": [["submit", 441533]], "time_left_end": "283", "answered_time": 441533, "user_answer": "22", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "283", "question_time_start": 441534, "question": "98+77", "correct_answer": 175, "events": [["submit", 453950]], "time_left_end": "270", "answered_time": 453950, "user_answer": "175", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "270", "question_time_start": 453950, "question": "84+18", "correct_answer": 102, "events": [["submit", 466124]], "time_left_end": "258", "answered_time": 466124, "user_answer": "102", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "258", "question_time_start": 466124, "question": "4+28+16", "correct_answer": 48, "events": [["submit", 470715]], "time_left_end": "254", "answered_time": 470715, "user_answer": "48", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "254", "question_time_start": 470716, "question": "4+4+4+17", "correct_answer": 29, "events": [["submit", 481172]], "time_left_end": "243", "answered_time": 481172, "user_answer": "29", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "243", "question_time_start": 481172, "question": "9+4+8+73", "correct_answer": 94, "events": [["submit", 497735]], "time_left_end": "227", "answered_time": 497735, "user_answer": "94", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "227", "question_time_start": 497736, "question": "43+46", "correct_answer": 89, "events": [["submit", 504099]], "time_left_end": "220", "answered_time": 504099, "user_answer": "89", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "220", "question_time_start": 504099, "question": "7+7+3+3", "correct_answer": 20, "events": [["submit", 507536]], "time_left_end": "217", "answered_time": 507536, "user_answer": "20", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 6, "start_time": 507536, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "217", "question_time_start": 507536, "question": "8+27+66", "correct_answer": 101, "events": [["submit", 516039]], "time_left_end": "208", "answered_time": 516039, "user_answer": "101", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "208", "question_time_start": 516040, "question": "3+6+6+99", "correct_answer": 114, "events": [["submit", 528384]], "time_left_end": "196", "answered_time": 528384, "user_answer": "114", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "196", "question_time_start": 528385, "question": "8+3+18", "correct_answer": 29, "events": [["submit", 540253]], "time_left_end": "184", "answered_time": 540253, "user_answer": "29", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "184", "question_time_start": 540253, "question": "4+3+7+77", "correct_answer": 91, "events": [["submit", 560772]], "time_left_end": "164", "answered_time": 560772, "user_answer": "87", "user_correct": "False", "score": "12"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "164", "question_time_start": 560772, "question": "94+64", "correct_answer": 158, "events": [["submit", 570505]], "time_left_end": "154", "answered_time": 570505, "user_answer": "158", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "154", "question_time_start": 570505, "question": "88+58", "correct_answer": 146, "events": [["submit", 584563]], "time_left_end": "140", "answered_time": 584563, "user_answer": "146", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "140", "question_time_start": 584563, "question": "6+9+97", "correct_answer": 112, "events": [["submit", 591683]], "time_left_end": "133", "answered_time": 591683, "user_answer": "112", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "133", "question_time_start": 591684, "question": "93+14", "correct_answer": 107, "events": [["submit", 597340]], "time_left_end": "127", "answered_time": 597340, "user_answer": "107", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "127", "question_time_start": 597340, "question": "3+6+7+6", "correct_answer": 22, "events": [["submit", 604784]], "time_left_end": "120", "answered_time": 604784, "user_answer": "22", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "120", "question_time_start": 604784, "question": "8+6+8+6", "correct_answer": 28, "events": [["submit", 608465]], "time_left_end": "116", "answered_time": 608465, "user_answer": "28", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 6, "start_time": 608466, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "116", "question_time_start": 608466, "question": "4+9+3+83", "correct_answer": 99, "events": [["submit", 616732]], "time_left_end": "108", "answered_time": 616732, "user_answer": "99", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "108", "question_time_start": 616733, "question": "6+8+6+48", "correct_answer": 68, "events": [["submit", 631305]], "time_left_end": "93", "answered_time": 631305, "user_answer": "68", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "93", "question_time_start": 631306, "question": "26+83", "correct_answer": 109, "events": [["submit", 638999]], "time_left_end": "85", "answered_time": 638999, "user_answer": "109", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "85", "question_time_start": 639001, "question": "7+87+86", "correct_answer": 180, "events": [["submit", 653170]], "time_left_end": "71", "answered_time": 653170, "user_answer": "180", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "71", "question_time_start": 653170, "question": "7+8+27", "correct_answer": 42, "events": [["submit", 659604]], "time_left_end": "65", "answered_time": 659604, "user_answer": "42", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "65", "question_time_start": 659605, "question": "7+3+9+7", "correct_answer": 26, "events": [["submit", 675035]], "time_left_end": "49", "answered_time": 675035, "user_answer": "27", "user_correct": "False", "score": "22"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "49", "question_time_start": 675035, "question": "13+94", "correct_answer": 107, "events": [["submit", 686879]], "time_left_end": "37", "answered_time": 686879, "user_answer": "107", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "37", "question_time_start": 686879, "question": "9+6+89", "correct_answer": 104, "events": [["submit", 695650]], "time_left_end": "29", "answered_time": 695650, "user_answer": "94", "user_correct": "False", "score": "22"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "29", "question_time_start": 695651, "question": "74+78", "correct_answer": 152, "events": [["submit", 707381]], "time_left_end": "17", "answered_time": 707381, "user_answer": "152", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "17", "question_time_start": 707383, "question": "7+6+3+8", "correct_answer": 24, "events": [["submit", 711104]], "time_left_end": "13", "answered_time": 711104, "user_answer": "24", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 6, "start_time": 711104, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "13", "question_time_start": 711104, "question": "3+3+9+77", "correct_answer": 92, "events": [["submit", 721786]], "time_left_end": "3", "answered_time": 721786, "user_answer": "92", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "3", "question_time_start": 721786, "question": "7+8+37", "correct_answer": 52, "events": []}}}}}